smartyhost.com.au 2005-06-15

# SmartyHost Privacy Policy

|   
---  
  
**150MB WEB HOSTING PACKAGE **  
With all the features you could possibly ask for in a web hosting package including 150 MB Web Space and 150 Email Accounts.  
  
**BARGAIN BASEMENT HOSTING**   
Everyone loves a bargain! Limited number of web hosting packages at very affordable prices from just $20 to $100 per year.  
  
**DOMAIN REGISTRATION**  
Don't pay too much for domain name registrations. Cheapest domains in Australia.   
  
New to SmartyHost! ADSL unlimited plans with no data charges, fixed monthly fees and Freebies. No hidden fees.  
  
**RESELLER WEB HOSTING**  
Offer SmartyHost affordable web hosting packages to your own clients. Includes up to 35% discount on all our packages.  

**FREE HOSTING TOOLS  
** Free resources include support forums, help files, control panel help, articles, and much more.  
  
**HOSTING ADD-ONS  
** View our new web hosting upgrades, advanced website statistical package, FormMail scripts, extra subdomains and more. ****  
  
**[HOSTING RENEWAL PAYMENT  
](https://ssl.smartyhost.com.au/billpayment.html)** Save time and money and pay your Web Hosting Renewal here. ****  
  
Home > Privacy Policy

**Information Collection** **and Use**  
Smartyhost Pty Ltd is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Pracsmart Pty Ltd collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

**Order**  
We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. 

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Sharing**  
We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we Pracsmart Pty Ltd are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Newsletter**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. 

**Security**  
This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web borrowers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just ‘surfing’.

| 

100% secure ordering
